JAMES WOLFE

THE BEST CODER



Wolfe.James.J96@gmail.com (703)789-0919 Northern Virginia Website Portfolio







SUMMARY

Computer Science graduate with a passion for problem-solving and learning, demonstrated experience in programming and customer service. Developed technical skill sets required to thrive in a professional work environment such as the AWS Cloud, web development, Linux, and computer technology troubleshooting.

SKILLS

- Joomla & WordPress **AWS Cloud Services** RedHat Hardware Troubleshooting
- Java & HTML SSH & CLI Linux CLI Sanding & Staining Wood

PROJECTS

Portfolios - Database Websites GitHub Repository

- Coded over four HTML, CSS, and Java-Script website templates then used database and publishing services like AWS S3, Azure Container, Surge, and GitHub Pages to launch the static websites.
- Wrote a custom domain name on Google Domains and pointed the Ips in the DNS record to GitHub pages.

Serverless Application GitHub Repository

- Typed NPM and Linux commands in the AWS Amplify CLI to launch an application then configured the server to connect to a GitHub repository.
- Downloaded the web-application through CODEPEN and created a repository and pushed the files to the main branch where the files are continually updated.

Headless Media Center

Using a Raspberry Pi, I mounted a disk image of Volumio to the device then configured the OS by connecting to the network and creating a login, after, I joined the hotspot using the application on a cellular device.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Woodworker Sue's Antiques

06/2021 — Present

After acquiring antique furniture and items, I refurbish and disassemble two to three pieces a week utilizing hand-on techniques then display a finished antique in a variety of store locations selling the highest quality antique refurbished antiques.

Data Technician CORESTAFF SERVICES

11/2020 - 12/2020

Worked through AWS Cloud troubleshooting tickets involving unable to POST and vital updates by rebooting servers, utilizing Linux update commands, reseating hardware and CAT5/6 cables, and other troubleshooting techniques.

Restaurant Server Mariachis TequliaRia & Restaurant

06/2018 - 01/2019

Served customers while multi-tasking food orders, drink and chip refills, and station clean-up in a fast-paced environment to provide the best customer service.

CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Cloud Practitioner

7BEZSG02PNEEQ83D

Agile Scrum Fundamentals

ude.my/UC-800faeff-a669-4e5b-b802-3cbb834cdd2f

Linux Administration Bootcamp

ude.my/UC-fcd5c324-ad8c-4b70-a83d-b9712cb3b0f8

EDUCATION

Computer Science, Northern Virginia Community College Computer Science, Assembly Language, and Calculus II

2016 - 2020